A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine Administration Electronic Files, Email, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, 2006-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)., Extent: 9480 emails.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Electronic Files, Subseries B. Amber Amato Email, 2006-2010 (bulk 2006-2009).
    - ALEE.PST, 2007-2010 (bulk 2007-2009).
      ALEE.PST contains 955 emails sent by Amber Amato (Lee) between July 2007 and January 2010. There are seven privacy protected and confidential emails in this PST file that are restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78, Types of restricted information may include, but are not limited to records containing personal information (health, social services and unemployment).
      Subjects include: constituent correspondence; weekly reports; gubernatorial flag orders; VIP correspondence report; and natural resources issues.
      Correspondents include: Chris Bast, Bennett Blodgett, Gena Boyle, Alicia Cavanaugh, Marc Cheatham, Jeff Corbin, Dustin Engels, Sherrie Harrington, Ryan Newcomb, Kate Paris, Svandis Pollard, Barbara Reese, Mark Rubin, Brian Shepard, Delacey Skinner, Lynda Tran, and Wayne Turnage.
    - KaineLibAAmato.pst, 2006-2010 (bulk 2006-2009).
      KaineLibAAmato.pst contains 437 emails sent and received by Amber Amato between January 2006 and January 2010. There are two worker's compensation claim emails in this PST file that are restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78.
      Subjects include: constituent correspondence; archiving the records of the Kaine administration; and gubernatorial flag orders.
      Correspondents include: Chris Bast, Ariel Billmeier, Marc Cheatham, Nikki Rovner, Brian Shepard, and Wayne Turnage,
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries C. Chris Bast Email, 2006-2009.
    This subseries contains 1188 emails in two PST files: CBAST.PST and KaineLibcbast.pst. Chris Bast held several positions during the Kaine administration. He served as a Special Assistant for Constituent Services from January 2006 to June 2007; Deputy Director of Constituent Services from June 2007 to December 2008; and Policy Analyst from December 2008 to November 2009. While in Constituent Services, Bast identified and handled VIP correspondence, tracked bills and responded to constituent inquiries on pending legislation, prepared weekly correspondence reports for the Governor, and was responsible for IQ Operations (database for tracking constituent correspondence). As a Policy Analyst, Bast advised the Governor on energy, elections, and administration policy issues.
    - CBAST.PST, 2006-2009.
      CBAST.PST contains 837 emails sent by Chris Bast between June 2006 and December 2009. There are seven privacy protected and confidential emails in this PST file that are restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78, Types of restricted information may include, but are not limited to records containing personal information (social services) and attorney-client communications.
      Subjects include: constituent correspondence; bill review; and energy and election issues.
      Correspondents include: Dustin Engels, Danielle Garrett, Alleyn Harned, Sherrie Harrington, Gordon Hickey, Michael Kelly, Jennie Moline, Jeff Reczek, Nikki Rovner, Mark Rubin, Brian Shepard, Delacey Skinner, Lynda Tran, and Wayne Turnage.
    - KaineLibcbast.pst, 2006-2009.
      KaineLibcbast.pst contains 351 emails sent and received by Chris Bast between January 2006 and August 2009.
      Subjects include: constituent correspondence; gubernatorial flag orders; bill review; and VIP correspondence report.
      Correspondents include: Amber Amato, Gena Boyle, Marc Cheatham, Wayne Turnage, Sara Wilson, and Richard Zorn.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries D. Aaron Larrimore Email, 2006-2007.
    This subseries contains 299 emails in one PST file: Personal Folders.pst. Aaron Larrimore served as Special Assistant for Constituent Services from January 2006 to August 2007. He also served as Special Assistant to Chief of Staff Wayne Turnage from May 2007 to August 2007.
    Personal Folders.pst contains 299 emails sent and received by Aaron Larrimore between January 2006 and July 2007. There is one social services related email in this PST file that is restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78.
    Subjects include: Constituent Services weekly reports (Thursday Report) and constituent correspondence.
    Correspondents include: Gena Boyle, Marc Cheatham, Sherrie Harrington, Amanda Howe, and Wayne Turnage.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries E. Ninette Linkous Email, 2007-2009.
    This subseries contains six emails in one PST file: KaineLibNLinkous.pst. Ninette Linkous served as Special Assistant for Constituent Services from 2006 to 2010. Linkous was responsible for document requests for birthdays, weddings, anniversaries and Boy and Girl Scouts.
    KaineLibNLinkous.pst contains six emails sent and received by Ninette Linkous between January 2007 and November 2009.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries F. Danielle Garrett Email, 2007-2009.
    This subseries contains 592 emails in two PST files: KaineLibDGarrett.pst and DGARRETT.PST. Danielle Garrett served as Special Assistant for Constituent Services from 2007 to 2009. Garrett was responsible for document requests for proclamations, and condolence and congratulation letters. She also compiled the Thursday Report and issue Tally Sheet.
    - KaineLibDGarrett.pst, 2007-2008.
      KaineLibDGarrett.pst contains 471 emails sent and received by Danielle Garrett between June 2007 and October 2008. There are three privacy protected and confidential emails in this PST file that are restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78, Types of restricted information may include, but are not limited to records containing personal information (social services) and judicial applications.
      Correspondents include: Amber Amato, Chris Bast, Gena Boyle, Beau Cribbs, Lauren Cunningham, Danielle Garrett, and Michael Kelly.
    - DGARRETT.PST, 2008-2009.
      DGARRETT.PST contains 121 emails sent and received by Danielle Garrett between October 2008 and April 2009. There is one health related email in this PST file that is restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78.
      Subjects include: constituent correspondence; and Constituent Services weekly reports (Thursday Report).
      Correspondents include: Amber Amato, Chris Bast, Brian Chiglinsky, and Dustin Engels.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries G. Jeff Reczek Email, 2007-2008.
    This subseries contains 77 emails in one PST file: KaineLibJReczek.pst. Jeff Reczek served as Special Assistant for Constituent Services from 2007 to 2008. Reczek was responsible for responding to correspondence related to issues that the governor did not have authority (localities, legislative branch, judicial branch, and independent agencies).
    KaineLibJReczek.pst contains 77 emails sent and received by Jeff Reczek between December 2007 and June 2008. There is one worker's compensation claim emails in this PST file that is restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78.
    Subjects include: constituent correspondence; and VIP correspondence report.
    Correspondents include: Chris Bast and Beau Cribbs.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries H. Dustin Engels Email, 2008-2009.
    This subseries contains 74 emails in one PST file: KaineLibdengels.pst. Dustin Engels served as Senior Special Assistant for Constituent Services from 2008 to 2010. Engels was responsible for proclamations.
    KaineLibdengels.pst contains 74 emails sent by Dustin Engels between July 2008 and December 2009.
    Correspondents include: Amber Amato and Kate Paris.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries I. Ryan Newcomb Email, 2008-2009.
    This subseries contains 132 emails in one PST file: KaineLibrnewcomb.pst. Ryan Newcomb served as Special Assistant for Constituent Services from 2008 to 2010. Newcomb was responsible for responding to correspondence related to issues that the governor did not have authority (localities and legal).
    KaineLibrnewcomb.pst contains 132 emails sent by Ryan Newcomb between December 2008 and December 2009.
    Subjects include: constituent services; and Constituent Services weekly reports (Thursday Report).
    Correspondents include: Amber Amato, Sherrie Harrington, and Megan Hershiser.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries J. Sasha Scott Email, 2008-2009.
    This subseries contains 750 emails in one PST file: KaineLibSScott.pst. Sasha Scott served as Special Assistant for Constituent Services from 2008 to 2010. Scott was responsible for responding to correspondence related to issues that the governor did not have authority (federal) as well as document requests for student, retirement, and church anniversary letters.
    KaineLibSScott.pst contains 750 emails sent and received by Sasha Scott between February 2008 and December 2009. Nearly all the emails are incoming constituent correspondence. There are three health related emails in this PST file that are restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries K. Megan Hershiser Email, 2008-2010.
    This subseries contains 28 emails in one PST file: MHERSHISER.PST. Megan Hershiser served as Special Assistant for Constituent Services from 2008 to 2010. Hershiser was responsible for responding to correspondence related to issues that the governor did not have authority (State Corporation Commission), Workman's compensation, and immigration.
    MHERSHISER.PST contains 28 emails sent by Megan Hershiser between October 2008 and January 2010.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries L. Katie Francis Email, 2008.
    This subseries contains 18 emails in two PST files: KaineLibkrancis.pst and KFRANCIS.PST. Katie Francis served as Special Assistant for Constituent Services in 2008.
    KaineLibkfrancis.pst contains 16 emails sent and received by Katie Francis between May 2008 and July 2008. KFRANCIS.PST contains two emails sent by Katie Francis on 31 July 2008.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries M. Luisa Soaterna Email, 2007, 2009-2010 (bulk 2009).
    This subseries contains 62 emails in two PST files: KaineLibLSoaterna.pst and LSOATERNA.PST. Luisa Soaterna served as Special Assistant for Constituent Services and Latino Liaison from 2009 to 2010. Soaterna previously worked in the Authentications Department of the Secretary of the Commonwealth.
    KaineLibLSoaterna.pst contains 57 emails sent and received by Lusia Soaterna in June 2007 and between April 2009 and January 2010. LSOATERNA.PST contains four emails sent by Lusia Soaterna between July 2009 and December 2009.
    Subjects include: Virginia Complete Count Committee; and Virginia Latino Advisory Board (VLAB).
    Correspondents include: Kris Tilley-Lubbs and Omar Rashid.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries N. Ryan Lodata Email, 2009.
    This subseries contains four emails in one PST file: KaineLibrlodata.pst. Ryan Lodata served as Special Assistant for Constituent Services from 2009 to 2010. Engels was responsible for congratulation and welcome message letters.
    KaineLibrlodata.pst contains four emails sent and received by Ryan Lodata between June 2009 and October 2009.
  - Series XIX. Constituent Services Office Electronic Files, Subseries O. Jose Guevara Email, 2009.
    This subseries contains 10 emails in one PST file: JGUEVARA.PST. Jose Guevara served as intern for Constituent Services in 2009.
    JGUEVARA.PST contains 10 emails sent by Jose Guevara between January 2009 and February 2009.
- Series XX. Other Electronic Files, 2006-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)., Extent: 1517 emails.
  The Other Electronic Files series contains the electronic communication for individuals whose email did not fit in any of the other series. This artificial series contains 1517 emails in ten (10) subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Amanda Howe Email, B. Tamra Talmadge-Anderson Email, C. Andrea Gaines Email, D. Andrew LeVasseur Email, E. Brianna Augenreich Email, F. Deanna Beacham Email, G. Jenna Baker Email, H. Jaime Stansbury Email, I. Laura Fields Email, and J. Luke Godwin Email.
  - Series XX. Other Electronic Files, Subseries A. Amanda Howe Email, 2007.
    Amanda Howe worked in the Office of Special Projects and was responsible for planning Queen Elizabeth's visit to Virginia in May 2007. Ahowe.pst contains 1008 emails sent and received by Amanda Howe between February 2007 and July 2007. See also Series III. Communications Office Electronic Files, Series K. Amanda Howe Email, 2009-2010.
    Subjects include: Queen Elizabeth's visit to Virginia in 2007.
    Correspondents include: Jean Bankos, Diane Bechamps, Amy Bridge, Erin Bryant, Rebecca Casson, Eliza Eversole, Cathy Ghidotti, Kevin Hall, Anne Holton, Bruce Jamerson, Aaron Larrimore, Bill Leighty, Dominic Martin, Jane Minerly, Susan Pollard, Delacey Skinner, and Tamra Talmadge-Anderson.
  - Series XX. Other Electronic Files, Subseries B. Tamra Talmadge-Anderson Email, 2007.
    Tamra Talmadge-Anderson worked in the Office of Special Projects and assisted with planning Queen Elizabeth's visit to Virginia in May 2007. Ttalmadge.pst contains 27 emails sent and received by Tamra Talmadge-Anderson between April 2007 and May 2007.
  - Series XX. Other Electronic Files, Subseries C. Andrea Gaines Email, 2006; 2009.
    Andrea Gaines served as Director of Virginia Corps from 2006 to 2010. KaineLibagaines.pst contains two emails received by Andrea Gaines in May 2006 and March 2009.
  - Series XX. Other Electronic Files, Subseries D. Andrew LeVasseur Email, 2009-2010 (bulk 2009).
    Andrew LeVasseur served as Executive Director of the Productivity Investment Fund. ALEVASSEUR.PST contains 94 emails sent by Andrew LeVasseur between July 2009 and January 2010.
  - Series XX. Other Electronic Files, Subseries E. Brianna Augenreich Email, 2009.
    Brianna Augenreich served as a Governor's Fellow in the Office of Commonwealth Preparedness during the summer of 2009. BAUGENREICH.PST contains 183 emails sent and received by Brianna Augenreich between May 2009 and October 2009.
  - Series XX. Other Electronic Files, Subseries F. Deanna Beacham Email, 2009-2010 (bulk 2009).
    Deanna Beacham served as an American Indian Specialist during the Kaine administration. DBEACHAM.PST contains 186 emails sent by Deanna Beacham between August 2009 and January 2010.
  - Series XX. Other Electronic Files, Subseries G. Jenna Baker Email, 2008.
    Jenna Baker served as Special Assistant to Virginia Lieutenant Governor Bill Bolling. JBAKER.PST contains two emails sent by Jenna Baker in February 2008.
  - Series XX. Other Electronic Files, Subseries H. Jaime Stansbury Email, 2007.
    Jaime Stansbury worked in the Governor's Office during 2007. JStansbury.pst contains nine emails sent and received by Jaime Stansbury between January 2007 and April 2007.
  - Series XX. Other Electronic Files, Subseries I. Laura Fields Email, 2009.
    Laura Fields served as Executive Assistant to the Director of the Executive Mansion from 2007 to 2010. KaineLiblfields.pst contains one emails sent by Laura Fields on 16 July 2009.
  - Series XX. Other Electronic Files, Subseries J. Luke Godwin Email, 2006.
    Luke Godwin served as an intern/fellow in the Governor's Office during 2006. Lgoodwin.pst contains five emails sent by Luke Godwin in August 2006.